expresspigeon.com 2015-03-17

# Privacy policy | ExpressPigeon

We are strongly committed to privacy and believe that good privacy is good business. Therefore, we have adopted this Privacy Policy for the ExpressPigeon.com website. You can link to this Privacy Policy directly from the website or through our Terms of Service. This Privacy Policy covers only the information collected on our website. It does not apply to any information collected offline. Please note that you cannot register for our service if you are under 18 years of age. 

## Information collection

### 1\. Personal Information

We request that you provide us with personal information when you subscribe to our services. This information may include among other things your name, address, email, password, occupation and any information you provide to us while using our services. We collect this information to allow our systems to function properly. We may also collect other information in connection with your log-in to and use of services and products on our website. This information may include IP address, type of browser and operating system and any other information that results from your interaction with our products or services. We do not presently nor will in the future share any personal information (whether provided to us or collected by us) with any Third Party. 

### 2\. Cookies

We use browser “cookies” to maintain session information and to allow for “remember me” function. None of the information in the cookies contains any personal or sensitive information about you. Please note that while most browsers will accept cookies by default, you may set your browser to reject cookies. However, disabling cookies in your browser will render our application inoperable. 

### 3\. Financial Information

We collect your financial information so that we can be compensated for paid services. We store this information with an industry trusted third party financial institution. This prevents any potential theft of such information even in the unlikely event of a security breach. The security of your financial data while in transmission is assured through a 128-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) connection between our Web server and a third party financial institution responsible for processing credit card transactions. 

### 4\. Contact List Information

You must comply with the Terms of Service and Use Agreement when you provide the contact details of your target audience to us. We reserve the right to monitor this information at any time in order to ensure your compliance with our Terms of Service. We also reserve the right to collect additional information about your contacts, including but not limited to IP address, browser type, email, client type and operating system. We do not presently nor will in the future share any contact information (whether provided to us or collected by us through subscription forms) with any Third Party. Contact list information is used strictly to fulfill the functionality of our systems. 

### 5\. Non-personally Identifiable Information

Our website may collect non-personally identifiable information. This may include, for example, collecting statistical information about the type of browsers people use to visit our website, domains from which our visitors come, or number of visits to our website, etc. This non-identifiable aggregate information may be used internally for quality control or for marketing purposes as well as provided to Third Parties. 

### 6\. Keeping personal information up to date

While we store your personal information in order to support the proper function of our applications, it is your responsibility to keep this information up to date. You may access your personal information at any time by logging into the website and navigating to My Account. 

### 7\. Email content

Please refer to Section 4 of the Terms of Service and Use Agreement to review the list of prohibited content. You may not use ExpressPigeon systems to send e-mails that include or link to any prohibited content. We reserve the right to monitor the content of your emails to ensure compliance with our Terms of Service, and freeze or even permanently close your account if we deem your content inappropriate, based solely on our opinion. 

### 8\. Exception from Coverage

This Privacy Policy places no duty upon us with respect to Confidential Information that (a) becomes generally known to the public without violation of this Policy; (b) is collected by us from a third party without a confidentiality obligation; (c) was independently developed by us without use of the Confidential Information; (d) is disclosed in response to a court or governmental order provided that we have given you prior written notice and opportunity to object; (e) to the extent that disclosure of such Confidential Information is necessary to enforce our rights under the Terms of Service and Use Agreement in connection with any litigation, arbitration or other dispute resolution procedure. 

### 9\. Information Protection

We represent that we will use commercially reasonable measures to maintain appropriate technical and organizational structure to protect any information, including personally-identifiable information that we collect, process or access against unauthorized or illegal processing or transfer and against accidental loss, access, or destruction. 

### 10\. Changes to this policy

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. We may or may not send updates by email, but the last updated date can be found at the bottom of this policy. Please feel free to come back to review the latest version. 

### 11\. Survival

The ExpressPigeon, Inc. duty to protect Confidential Information shall survive the expiration or termination of the Terms of Service and Use Agreement for any reason and will extend for a period of 5 (five) years from the date of disclosure by you or collection by us of Confidential Information. 

### 12\. Incorporation by Reference.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into the ExpressPigeon, Inc. Terms of Service and Use Agreement and, therefore, made part of the Agreement. 

## Contact us

In case you have questions or suggestions regarding this policy, feel free to contact us using our Support page, or write to: 

Privacy   
**ExpressPigeon, Inc.**   
113 N. McHenry #128   
Buffalo Grove, IL 60089 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on December 11, 2011
